// list of questions to display on quiz
var questions = [{
    "question": "Who is the first Indian to win a Nobel Prize?",
    "option1": "Rabindranath Tagore",
    "option2": "CV Raman",
    "option3": "Mother Theresa",
    "option4": "Hargobind Khorana",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "This Pen is much ......... than that.",
    "option1": "more cheaper",
    "option2": "the cheaper",
    "option3": "cheaper",
    "option4": "cheapest ",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "How will our sun end up it's life after around 6 billion years?",
    "option1": "black hole",
    "option2": "neutron star",
    "option3": "pulsar",
    "option4": "white dwarf",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "Which of the following is the oldest test cricket playing country in the world?",
    "option1": "India",
    "option2": "Australia",
    "option3": "England",
    "option4": "New zealand",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "He told me that he …… watching the movie.",
    "option1": "is finished",
    "option2": "was finished",
    "option3": "had finished",
    "option4": "not finished",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "Speed of a car is 60 km/hr. Distance covered in 1 ¼ hours is ……… ",
    "option1": "60",
    "option2": "65",
    "option3": "70",
    "option4": "75",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "Which cricketer had scored highest individual score in ODI cricket?",
    "option1": "Rohit sharma",
    "option2": "Chris gayle",
    "option3": "Martin guptill",
    "option4": "Virat kohli",
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question": "How many galaxies can be seen with naked eye from the earth? ",
    "option1": "25",
    "option2": "4",
    "option3": "0",
    "option4": "1",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "Which among the following is the smallest bird in the world?",
    "option1": "Pardalote",
    "option2": "Goldcrest",
    "option3": "Hummingbird",
    "option4": "Wee Bill",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": " If David’s age is 27 years old in 2011. What was his age in 2003?",
    "option1": "17 years",
    "option2": "18 years",
    "option3": "15 years",
    "option4": "19 years",
    "answer": "4"
}]